

## **Profile**

I have honed my ability to align the team to work towards common goals. Demonstrated history working in various domains. Finance, automotive, and Media industry.

I believe there is always something to learn, and with growing data analytics, there's always something new! I enjoy collaborating with others to gain different perspectives to refine strategies.

Industry experienced Senior Global Data Manager for Paramount Pictures. Skilled in the development of projects in Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud services, Snowflake, Big query, Data bricks, and integration of data systems for BI reporting in Tableau. Motivated executing projects in Agile methodologies and agile sprints.

# **Employment History**

Senior Manager, Global Data Technologies, Paramount Pictures, Hollywood

JUNE 2019 - PRESENT

- Maintaining large data engineering teams working on multiple data warehousing projects.
- Managing BI projects for domestic and international markets for subscription video on demand (SVOD), collecting and transforming subscriber and financial data based on demographics across the entire organization.
- Developed an enterprise data model that integrated data from multiple sources and enabled consistent data access across the organization.
- Establishing data engineering solutions in AWS, Snowflake, PostgreSQL, Google Cloud Portal, and Data Bricks.

#### Technology lead - US Engineering, Infosys Limited, Los Angeles

MARCH 2016 - JUNE 2019

- Leading BI and Data Warehousing team for equity asset management in Charles River development.
- Conducted requirement analysis, Gap analysis, Incident Management, Problem Management, Troubleshooting Methodologies, and in-depth knowledge of all stages of the software development life cycle (SDLC).

Principal Business Intelligence Developer, Manheim Auctions, Atlanta
APRIL 2015 – MARCH 2016

Business Intelligence Developer, LocalEdge Media Services, Buffalo
MARCH 2014 - APRIL 2015

### **Education**

Master of Science - Computer Engineering, Wright State University

Bachelor of Engineering, Visvesvaraya Technological University

#### Courses

AWS Solution Architect- Associate (v.2018)

JULY 2018 - JULY 2020

#### **Details**

Los Angeles United States 937-802-6469 huruliashish@gmail.com

## Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Resume

#### Skills

SQL

Python

Snowflake Data Warehousing

**Databricks** 

**Amazon Cloud Services** 

Microsoft Excel

**Google Cloud Services** 

Agile Methodologies

Kubernetes

Big Data Management